《诉讼双雄》前情提要
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
也许我们可以一起玩玩
I thought it might be nice to get out there
认识认识
and get to know each other.
你其实想说
I think what you really mean
你想给新的执行合伙人留个好印象
is you'd like to impress the new managing partner.
首席翻译官
█ 网易见外
要是我真是这么想的呢
And what if I did?
如果你想给我留下好印象
You wanna impress me?
给我找一个牛逼的客户来
Do it with a big, fat client.
赞恩许诺了萨曼莎接下来让她的名字上墙
Zane promised Samantha she'd be the next Name Partner.
首席校对官
人人译视界
·
人人
你跟他说你也保证了亚历克斯了吗
And did you tell him that you made the same promise to Alex?
没有
No, I didn't.
翻译     小僵僵   辰星晓Reginamoon  苏葵   小溪1120
你想跟我开战
You wanna take me on,
你尽管来  我坐的这个位子
you go for it, 'cause I didn't get where I am
可不是随便让人威胁拿来的
by letting people like you push me around.
大卫·福克斯想打一架  我奉陪
David Fox wants a fight and I'm gonna give him one.
翻译     Giggles  斗斗  Lynn_宁  木浅  暴走小罐头
为什么
A fight about what?
他不想给清洁女工付加班费
He doesn't want to pay our cleaning woman overtime.
校对     木浅
哈维  这不是我们的行事风格
Harvey, this isn't what we do.
迈克就会这么做
Mike would have done it.
迈克已经不在这了
And Mike's not here anymore
因为他最终想要做的
because he finally came to terms with the fact
时间轴     张小满   caroline
和我们不同
that this isn't what we do.
而我是不会同意仅仅因为你觉得
I'm not gonna let us start losing clients
清洁工人比公司的需要还重要
because you decided the cleaning staff
就让我们产生客户流失的
is more important than the needs of this firm.
后期     斯人
我没做任何你没批准的事
I didn't do anything that you didn't sign off on.
够了  你不能因为这种小事
That's enough. You don't go to war
总监     木浅
就和这栋楼的所有人开战
with the guy that owns your house over something like this.
把它解决掉  就今天
End it, and end it today.
我想跟你要个完美的孩子
I wanna make a perfect baby with you.
┌
┐
└
┘
人人影视官方客户端
唯一下载渠道
app.YYeTs.com
┌
┐
└
┘
-你确定吗  -确定
- Are you sure? - Absolutely.
我不想只是停止预防措施
And I don't want to just pull the goalie.
我想努力尝试
I want to start trying,
我想现在就开始尝试
and I want to start trying right now.
你还记得你之前告诉我你答应萨曼莎
Do you remember when you told me, you promised Samantha
-她会成为下一个冠名合伙人  -记得
- her name would go up next? - I did.
我也向亚历克斯承诺过
I made Alex the same promise.
那在我看来只有一个办法
Then I guess there's only one thing to do.
"踢皮球"
Kick the can down the road.
我知道你认为我们是在竞争同一件事
I know you think we're in competition for the same thing,
但不是的
but we're not.
罗伯特·赞恩对我做出了承诺
Robert Zane made me a promise.
下一个上墙的名字一定是我的
The next name that goes up on the wall is mine.
小兔子绕树跳了一圈
Bunny rabbit goes around the tree once...
小兔子绕树跳了两圈
bunny rabbit goes around the tree twice...
小兔子  小兔子  想来点好玩的吗
And I say bunny rabbit, bunny rabbit, wanna play nice?
希拉  你在做什么
Sheila, what are you doing?
我在"守株待兔"
I'm hunting "Wabbits."
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
别用福德先生
Not Fudd.
你知道我无法拒绝埃尔默·福德先生
You know I can't resist Elmer Fudd.
埃尔默·福德: 美国动画人物  和兔八哥是死敌
为什么要拒绝呢
Why would you want to?
我的天  希拉  现在不行
Oh, my God, Shelia, i cannot right now.
为什么
Why not?
因为我要见客户
Because I have a client meeting,
不只是我  赞恩也来
and it's not just me. Zane's coming too.
所以无论你想做什么  都要等一下
So whatever you had in mind, it's going to have to wait.
好吧
All right.
我不想这么做  但是
I didn't want to have to do this, but...
我正在排卵期
I'm fertile...
我成熟的小卵子正等着筛选
and I am ripe for the picking.
所以我不管你有什么会议
So I don't care whether you have a meeting or not.
我需要你给我"播种"
I'm going to need your Johnny Appleseed.
希拉  你知道
Sheila, you know if there's one thing
比埃尔默·福德更能挑逗我的
that revs me up more than Elmer Fudd
就是美国神话英雄了
it's American folk heroes.
我想是时候让保罗·班杨拿出斧子
Then I think it's time for Paul Bunyan
保罗·班杨: 美国神话人物  巨人樵夫  力大无穷
向森林进军了
to march across that forest and take out his axe.
我要来点更猛的
Oh, I'm gonna do more than that.
-不要  -我就要
- You wouldn't. - I would,
是时候让约翰·亨利摇起他威猛的铁锤了
because it's time for John Henry to swing the mighty hammer.
约翰·亨利: 美国神话人物  黑人钢铁工匠
你知道了吗
Did you know?
-知道什么  -萨曼莎得到赞恩的晋升
- Know what? - That Zane promised Samantha
她是下一个冠名合伙人
she was the next Name Partner.
亚历克斯  来我的办公室
Alex, let's go back up to my office.
看起来你想要喝一杯
Sounds like you could use a drink.
我只想要你坦白地告诉我
What I could use is some God damn honesty.
-你知道这件事吗  -我知道
- Did you know? - Yeah, I knew.
那你为什么不告诉我
Then why the hell didn't you tell me?
因为还没有人作出决定
Because no one's deciding anything right now
我不想无缘无故让你烦恼
and I didn't want to upset you for no reason.
无缘无故吗  赞恩已经保证...
No reason? Zane promised his right hand--
我知道他作出保证了
I know what he promised.
但你还有我和路易
But look, you got me and you got Louis.
二比一
That's two against one.
等时机成熟  我们的投票能压住他的
When the time is right, we'll out-vote him.
到底何时算时机成熟
And when exactly is the time going to be right?
六个月  一年  还是三年
Six months? A year? Three years?
-亚历克斯  -不  哈维  我要知道
- Alex-- - No, Harvey, I want to know
你到底什么时候
when you're planning on getting the balls
有胆量对抗赞恩
to stand up to that man and what exactly
同时我需要做什么
I'm supposed to do in the meantime.
我来告诉你你该做什么
I'll tell you what you're supposed to do.
你应该有信心  坐观其变
You're supposed to have faith and sit tight.
如果换位思考  你还坐得住吗
And if you were in my position, would you sit tight?
可能不容易  但我会那么做
It may not be easy but, yeah, I would.
真可笑  我还记得你几年前和我处境相同
That's funny, because I recall you were in a similar position
那时是和杰西卡  与其坐观其变
years ago with Jessica, and instead of sitting tight,
你直接让我介绍另一份工作给你
you came to me looking for another job.
-罗伯特  韦恩怎么样  -我来告诉你
- Robert, how's Wayne? - I'll tell you how he is.
他被告了  他想知道
He's getting sued, and he wants to know
- 他的律师跑哪里去了  -好吧
- why his lawyer's not here. - All right,
再等十分钟  我马上到了
just hold down the fort for ten more minutes, I'm almost there.
我没问你何时到
I didn't ask you when you'd get here,
路易  我想问你去哪了
Louis I asked you where you were.
有些私事
That's, uh, kind of personal.
我觉得不太好  路易
Well, I feel kind of bad about that, Louis,
我在这白白站了三十分钟
but I've been standing here with nothing
但我在这干等了三十分钟了
but my dick in my hand for the last 30 minutes.
好吧  如果你非要知道
All right, well, if you wanna know,
希拉和我想要孩子
Sheila and I are trying to have a baby
但她不再年轻了
and she's not getting any younger,
所以我们要抓住每一次机会
and we're just trying to take advantage of any opportunity we can.
你怎么不早说
Why didn't you say so?
赶紧过来吧
Just get here as fast as you can.
像我说的  十分钟见
Like I said, I'll see you in ten.
-兄弟  -怎么了
- Hey, buddy. - Yeah?
你知道这附近哪有来爱德吗
You know where a Rite Aid is around here?
抱歉  我也不是本地人
No, I'm sorry, I'm actually not from around here--
我才不管你住哪里
I don't give a shit where you live.
照我说的做  否则就挨子弹
Do what I say and you won't get shot.
-感觉到了吗  -是的  感觉到了
- You feel me? - Yeah, I feel you,
-感受到了  -很好  走吧
- I feel you, I feel you. - Good, let's walk.
趴到地上  不准看我
Get on the ground, and don't you fucking look at me.
-好  好  -钱包和手机
- Okay, okay. - Wallet and phone.
-手机呢  -钱包里有一千美元
- Where's the phone? - There's $1,000 in there,
够  够了吗
is that--is that not enough?
你以为我是来谈判的吗
You think we're negotiating, here?
不不  只是手机里有些照片
No, no, no, it's just that there--there's pictures
我还没来得及备份
on my phone that I haven't backed up.
关我屁事
I don't give a shit!
手机给你
Here's my phone.
趴下
Stay down.
不准动
Don't even move.
*给你太太再拿块馅饼*
♪ Get another piece of pie for your wife ♪
*所有人都想知道那感觉*
♪ Everybody wanna know how it feel ♪
*所有人都想见见那景象*
♪ Everybody wanna see what it's like ♪
*豆子馅饼我也愿吃  我不在乎*
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie, I don't mind ♪
*我和妹子忙着赚钱*
♪ Me and Missy is so busy, busy making money ♪
*好了*
♪ All right ♪
*退开点  我要跳舞*
♪ All step back, I'm 'bout to dance ♪
诉讼双雄
第八季  第四集
*美钞爵士摇摇摇*
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
该死
Shit...
路易  你不是要和罗伯特·赞恩出去吗
Louis, aren't you supposed to be out with Robert Zane?
我发誓  如果你像上次那样
I swear, if you cancelled that dinner
因为他们没有辣椒粉而取消晚餐的话
because they ran out of paprika like last time I--
我的天哪  发生什么了  路易
Oh, my God. What happened, Louis?
-没什么  -没什么
- Nothing. - Nothing?
你看上去像被车撞了
You look like you've been hit by a car.
一个男的抢了我的钱包和手机
A guy took my wallet and my phone.
我不知道该怎么办  所以来这儿了
I didn't know what to do, so I--I came here.
好吧  我先给希拉打电话  然后罗伯特
All right, I'm calling Sheila and then Robert and--
谁也不许联系  格蕾琴
You're not calling anyone, Gretchen.
我不希望罗伯特知道
I don't want Robert to know.
你得告诉他发生了什么
You have to tell him what happened.
我不能
I can't.
-为什么  -因为他是新的执行合伙人
- Why not? - Because he's my new managing partner
我不希望他认为我是个怂货
and I do not want him to know that I am weak.
路易  你不怂
Louis, you are not weak.
谁都可能遇到这事
It could have happened to anybody.
-罗伯特也可能遇上  -是啊  但并没有
- it could have happened to him. - Yeah, but it didn't.
我却碰上了  所以我不想告诉他
It happened to me, and that's why I don't want to tell him.
你打算怎么办
Well, what are you gonna do?
他肯定会问你  为什么没出席会议
'Cause he's gonna wanna know why you didn't show up to that meeting.
我就让他
I'm going to let him--
认为是他以为知道的事情吧
think what he already thinks.
希拉和我打算要孩子
That Sheila and I were trying to have a child,
比计划多花了些时间
it took longer than we thought--
-路易  -格雷琴  我不想再说了
- Louis. - Gretchen, I'm done talking about this.
放我一马可以吗
Can you just please let me be?
好吧  路易  我不告诉别人
Okay, Louis, I won't tell anybody.
但处理好伤口前我也不会离开
I'm not going anywhere until we patch you up.
如果你不小心  卖百吉饼的家伙
If you're not careful, the bagel guy's
会发现你在外面偷腥
going to figure out you're cheating on him.
-谁说这不是百吉饼了  -那个说
- Who says this isn't a bagel? - Same person who says
你只有五岁小孩幽默感的人
you've got the sense of humor of a five-year-old.
我要在休息室揪你的小辫子
I am so going to pull your pigtails at recess.
你是想接着说闲话
Okay, do you want to keep going,
还是让我问个正经问题
or can I ask you a serious question?
-你想听实话吗  -不
- You want the truth? - No.
我想让你多接些公益诉讼案
I want to talk to you about doing more pro bonos.
-唐娜  -哈维  听我说
- Donna. - Harvey, listen to me.
那个清洁工的案子对你有好处
That cleaning woman's case was good for you,
尽管迈克不在这里了
and even though Mike's not here,
我觉得我们应该接着做
I think we should keep doing them.
唐娜  也许我是想念迈克  但我不是他
Donna, I might be missing Mike, but I'm not Mike,
一小时内我还有个会议
and I have a meeting in an hour.
但如果你想接公益诉讼  你去接
But if you want to take on a pro bono, knock yourself out.
我确实想  如果你不想做
You know what, I do, and if you don't want it,
-那我去找亚历克斯  -不行
- I'm just going to go ask Alex. - Not Alex.
-他没有心情  -为什么
- He's not in the mood. - Why not?
他发现昨晚赞恩答应萨曼莎做冠名合伙人
He found out about Zane promising Samantha Name Partner last night.
你说什么了
What did you say to him?
你觉得我说什么了  我让他老实待着
What do you think I said? I told him to sit tight.
你那时候老实待着了吗
Did you sit tight when you were in the same position?
他也是这么说的
That's what he said.
如果你不想让他和你一样
Then if you don't want him doing what you did,
另谋高就
which is go looking for another job,
那我建议你做些能留住他的事
then I suggest you do something that makes him want to stay.
现在我要去问卡特里娜
Now, I'm going to go ask Katrina
她是否想做公益诉讼
if she wants to do a pro bono.
我不管代价是什么
I don't care what it takes.
你把他带到那个法官前
You get him in front of that judge,
我会让他摆脱困境的
I'll get him off the hook.
很好
Good.
不管你在做什么
Whatever you're cooking,
我需要你先着手做这个集体诉讼案
I need you to bump this class action to the front of the line.
-集体诉讼  -是啊  怎么了
- Class action? - Yeah, why?
-有问题吗  -没有问题
- You got a problem with that? - No problem,
但是诉讼并非我的专长
but litigation isn't my specialty
这你也知道  所以到底什么事
and you know it, so what's going on?
事情就是
What's going on is,
这以前是路易·利特的案子  现在归你了
this was louis Litt's case and now it's yours.
对此路易·利特怎么想呢
And how does Louis Litt feel about that?
他怎么想我才不在乎
I don't give a shit about how he feels.
可我在乎
Well, I do.
我刚在这里立住脚
I just got on good footing around here,
我可不想功亏一篑  现在我得...
I'm not looking to undo it. Now I got to get to--
等等  你是我最后的指望
Hold on, now. You are my go-to.
别跟我玩办公室斗争这一套
Don't start playing office politics on me.
罗伯特  我是为了你才明争暗斗
Robert, I played office politics for you
斗了好多年  你可别忘了
for years, in case you forgot.
我没忘  但他爽约了
I didn't, but the man pulled a no-show
而且见的是他自己的客户
to a meeting with his own client
而我要让他知道知道厉害  你参不参加
and I need to send a message, so are you in or out?
好吧  罗伯特  我参加
Okay, Robert. I'm in.
我相信你的事一定很重要  哈维
I'm sure whatever it is is very important, Harvey,
但我现在有点忙
but I'm a little busy right now.
亚历克斯  你说得对  要是我是你
Alex, you were right. If I were in your shoes,
我也不会坐以待毙
sitting tight wouldn't fly with me either.
我想了一下  想出了一个主意
I thought about it, and I got an idea.
如果这主意不是你和路易去告诉赞恩
Well, if it isn't you and Louis telling Zane
下一个就轮到我了  那我可不一定会喜欢
my number's up next, I'm not sure I'm going to like it.
这主意是  你去做一件事
What it is is you doing something
好让赞恩注意到你
to put you on the map with Zane.
帕克森生物科技
Paxson BioScience.
这家公司很大  油水多
They're big, they're juicy,
而且我们一个半小时后就要和他们开会了
and we got a meeting with them in a half an hour.
-我们  -没错  我们
- We? - Yeah, we.
那就算了  如果签他们的不是我一个人
Then forget it, because if I don't sign them alone,
罗伯特是不会注意的
Robert's not going to care.
亚历克斯  我已经尽我所能了
Alex, I'm doing the best I can right now.
他们点名要我去  要是我不出面
They're expecting me. I don't show up,
场面上肯定过不去
it's not going to look right.
真是什么事你都能找出一套说辞
You've got an answer for everything, don't you?
我们就下楼去
Let's just go down there
拿下他们不好吗
and lock these guys down.
这之后我保证  你是他们的正式律师
After that, you have my word. You're the attorney of record.
好吧  哈维  咱们去拿下他们
All right, Harvey. Let's go lock them down.
卡丽  我是哈维·斯佩克特
Carrie, Harvey Specter.
这是我的搭档  亚历克斯·威廉姆斯
This is my partner, Alex Williams.
抱歉  我还以为会议只有我们两人参加
I'm sorry, I was thinking it was just going to be the two of us.
没事的
It's okay.
你能告诉我的事
Anything you can say in front of me,
都能对亚历克斯说
you can say to Alex.
那样的话
In that case...
克莱托公司
CrytoGen.
这家公司价值八千万
They're worth 80 million,
但他们坐拥价值数十亿未开发知识产权
but they're sitting on billions of undeveloped IP.
我尝试收购这家公司已经两年了
I've been trying to buy them for two years.
让我猜猜  为了逼他们出售公司
Let me guess, you've used every tactic in the book
所有的正经办法你都用尽了
to force them to sell.
现在你想尝试一些
Now you're looking to try some
不太光彩的手段
that aren't in the book.
不妨这么说  在15家有专业能力
Let's just say that of the 15 companies
在这一行业进行投资的公司中
that specialize in financing that industry,
已经有14家一夜之间被逐出
14 have suddenly found themselves out
克莱托公司的生意了
of the CrytoGen business.
而这第15家公司恰好就是我们的客户
And isn't it the strangest coincidence
这个巧合是不是也太奇怪了
that the 15th just so happens to be one of our clients?
上天自有其安排
The Lord works in mysterious ways.
请说明白  你是在要求我们
Just to be clear, are you asking us
对我们的客户施加压力
to pressure one of our clients
让其切断这家公司的救命稻草吗
into cutting off this company's lifeline?
因为这样可就有违法律了
Because that would be against the law.
我没有要求你做任何事
I'm not asking you to do anything.
但如果真发生了这种事
But were that to happen,
你们会发现自己突然多了一个大客户
you'd suddenly find yourself with a huge new client.
我觉得这听起来还挺有趣的
I'd say that sounds pretty interesting.
可我觉得这就是胡扯  不会发生这种事的
And I say bullshit. It's not going happen.
最好还是发生吧
Well it better,
因为这就是我们谈成生意的代价
because that's what it's going to take to get our business.
亚历克斯  不如我们听听她都要...
Alex, why don't we listen to what she has to say--
不  哈维  我不想为这群人违背法律底线
No, Harvey, I'm not looking to cross the line for these guys,
我更不在乎他们是不是
and I don't care if they tell me
会保证预付一年的佣金
they'll guarantee a year's retainer in advance.
要是我告诉你
And what if I told you
这比预付款比得上你们出价最高的客户呢
that retainer would match your highest-billing client?
我觉得这是个错误  但我们要是想做这事
Look, I think it's a mistake, but if we're going do this,
就需要了解我们将要插手的是什么
we need to know what we're getting involved in.
他说的对  你想让我们冒险
He's right. You want us to risk this,
我们就需要了解被你们切断的
we need to knew every source of funding
每一笔资金的来源
you choked off from these guys,
以及你们所做过的所有其他不光彩的事
and every other shady thing you've done,
因为正如他所说
because like he said,
我得清楚地知道
I need to know exactly
自己插手的到底是怎么回事
what I'm getting myself involved in.
那明天之前我们会把一切信息
Then we'll have everything over to you
都告知给你
by the end of the day.
-罗伯特  有空吗  -没有  路易
- Robert, got a sec? - No, Louis, I don't.
听着  我知道我说会迟到一会儿
Look, I know I said that I'd be a little late--
但你却决定去哄女朋友
But instead you decided to tap your girlfriend
而不是来做你该死的工作
instead of doing your God damn job.
罗伯特  我说过了  我们在努力要孩子
Robert, I told you, we're trying to have children.
你还说过你在来开会的路上
You also told me you were on your way to the meeting,
而我可不喜欢让人骗
and I don't appreciate being lied to.
好吧  听我说
Okay, listen to me.
我知道我缺席了  但这不重要
I know I didn't show up, but it doesn't matter
因为不论他们有什么问题  我都能处理
because whatever their issue is I can handle it.
不劳您大驾了  因为我已经处理好了
You don't have to handle it because I already did.
你这话什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
意思是今天早晨
It means that as of this morning,
是萨曼莎·惠勒处理了这件事
Samantha Wheeler is handling the matter,
这样你就有足够的时间照顾家庭了
so you have plenty of time for your family planning.
我是冠名合伙人  这是我最老的客户之一
I am Name Partner. This is one of my oldest clients.
你不能这样对我
You cannot do this to me.
不是我这样对你
I didn't do this to you.
而是你自己放我鸽子
You did it to yourself when you hung me out to dry.
罗伯特  拜托
Robert, please.
你不了解全情
You don't know the whole story.
我知道了所有我该知道的
I know all I need to know.
现在滚出我办公室  别再对我撒谎
Now get out of my office and don't ever lie to me again.
格蕾琴  我要你马上去档案室
Gretchen I need you to the file room right away
让所有关于
and make every document
麦金利服装公司的文件都消失
we have on McKinley Outfitters disappear.
办不到  路易  我一小时前得到指示
Can't do that, Louis. I got instructions to send them
把它们送去萨曼莎·惠勒的办公室
over to Samantha Wheeler's office an hour ago.
什么  你怎么能这样对我
What? How could you do that to me?
因为罗伯特·赞恩站在这里
Because Robert Zane stood here
亲自给我下达了命令
and gave me an order himself.
-我能有什么选择  -该死
- What choice did I have? - God damn it.
路易  我没告诉他发生了什么
Louis, I didn't tell the man what happened
因为我答应你不说  但他因为
because I promised I wouldn't, but he's punishing you
一件不值得受罚的事情惩罚你
for something you don't deserve to be punished for,
所以你干嘛不直接告诉他
so why don't you just tell him?
我不能显得软弱
I'm not going to look weak.
由于你没勇气对他说实话
Well, having him take your client
而让他抢走了你的客户
because you don't have the courage to tell him the truth
也没让你显得强大
doesn't exactly make you look strong.
那我要把客户抢回来
Well, then I need to take my client back.
你要怎么做
How the hell are you going to do that?
很简单  她是个爱交易的女人
Easy. She's a transactional woman.
我就告诉她我欠她一次
I'll just tell her I owe her one.
你是叫她违抗赞恩吗
And you ask her to go against Zane?
那你不如叫她自取灭亡好了
You might as well ask her to set herself on fire.
或许你可以帮帮我
Well, maybe if you'd God damn help me
而不是告诉我我有多软弱
instead of telling me how weak I am,
说不定我们还能想出点办法
maybe we could figure something out.
路易  我是在帮你
Louis, I am trying to help you.
如果你看不出来  那就是有问题
And if you can't see that, then something's wrong.
格蕾琴  拜托  只有你知道
Gretchen, please. You're the only one who knows
我昨晚失去尊严的事
that I had my dignity taken last night.
我不能失去第二次
I can't have it taken again.
好吧  路易
All right, Louis.
我要帮你  就得知道
I help you with this, I need to know
你能振作起来
that you're going to be able to keep it together.
我只需要抢回我的客户
All I need is to take my client back.
-仅此而已  -好
- That's all I need. - Okay.
依我看  你想抢回麦金利
As I see it, you want McKinley back?
你就要把那个女人置于
You need to put that woman in a position
她别无选择的处境
where she doesn't have any choice.
我听起来像帕克森生物科学的那帮好伙计
Sounds to me like the good folks at Paxson BioScience
整天忙得团团转
have been some busy little beavers.
你跟我想的一样吗
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
当然  如果他们愿意做这些见不得人的勾当
I sure am. If they're willing to do all this shady shit
因为克莱托公司有着数十亿的未来收益
because CrytoGen has billions in future revenue--
我们干嘛不绕开见不得人的勾当
Why don't we skip the shady shit
现在就去为克莱托公司辩护呢
and go represent CrytoGen right now?
没错  而且我们有办法
Exactly. And we got the road map
让他们在途中摆脱麻烦
to keeping them out of trouble on its way.
亚历克斯  你太狡诈了
Alex, you are one devious mother----er.
谢谢  我就当是夸我了
Thanks, I'll take that as a compliment.
那你还真是个十足的混蛋
In that case, you're a real asshole of a guy, too.
说真的  哈维
Seriously, Harvey.
我们在利用会议期间
We're using information they gave us
他们透露的信息
in the context of a meeting.
这本身就不太光明
That's a little shady itself.
-你确定没关系吗  -当然
- You sure you're okay with it? - I am.
再说  他们能怎么做
Besides, what are they gonna do?
报警说他们叫我们去抢银行
Tell the police they asked us to rob a bank
等他们到银行时  我们已经把钱偷光了吗
and by the time they got there, we moved all the money?
那唯一要做的就是关掉克莱托公司
Then the only thing left to do is close CrytoGen.
-好  我来搞定  -不
- All right, I'll set it up. - No.
你需要参加上一次会议
You needed to be at that last meeting.
而不必插手这件事
You don't need to be at this one.
-亚历克斯  -哈维  别忘了
- Alex-- - Harvey, let's not forget
你来找我的初衷
why you came to me with this.
这件事让我来办
Let me bring this one home.
好吧  都交给你了
All right. They're all yours.
-你想见我吗  -对
- You wanted to see me? - I did.
很高兴  因为我听说
Well, I'm glad you did, because I heard
你把路易的一个客户给了萨曼莎
that you gave one of Louis's clients to Samantha
我不想告诉你要如何经营律所  罗伯特
and I don't want to tell you how to run the firm, Robert,
但我认为这是个坏主意
but I think that's a bad idea.
我不是想谈这个
Well, that's not exactly what I wanted to talk about,
但我觉得这是个好话题
but I think it's a good platform.
-我没听懂  -你或许不想告诉我
- I don't follow. - You may not want to tell me
怎么做好我的工作  但我要告诉你
how to do my job, but I'm going to tell you
-如何做好你的  -什么
- how to do yours. - Excuse me?
你是不是未经我允许
Did you assign Katrina Bennett
给了卡特里娜·班尼特一个无偿服务案
a pro bono without running it by me?
我不知道我有必要经你允许
I didn't know that I needed to run it by you.
在客户恰好和我想签约客户
You do when that client happens to conflict
有冲突时就有必要
with someone I'm trying to sign.
我不知道他们有冲突
I didn't know they did.
也正因此你不跟我商量
Which is why you run it by me.
更重要的是  一间律所的首席运营官
And was is more important is what is a COO
不该一开始就放掉
of a law firm doing handing out pro bonos
无偿服务案吗
in the first place?
我只是认为这能...
I just thought that it was good--
这是个反问句  唐娜
It's a rhetorical question, Donna.
-我不在乎你怎么想  -明白
- I don't care what you thought. - Understood.
-说完了吗  -没说完
- Is that all? - No, it's not.
一个首席运营官应该做的是
What a COO should be doing
最大化我们每平方英尺的收益
is maximizing our revenue per square foot,
这需要先评估现在每平方英尺的收益
which starts by an assessment of our revenue per square foot.
我还真不是做这个的
Well, that's not really what I do.
现在是了  明天下班前
It is now. I want a report on my desk
我要看到报告
by end of day tomorrow.
这和路易有关吗
Does this have anything to do with Louis?
-因为我不认为  -这关系到路易对我撒谎
- Because I don't think-- - It has to do with Louis lying to me,
哈维和房东起冲突
and Harvey getting into it with the landlord,
然后现在又是你  这一切都表明
and now you, which all adds up
这家律所的运作方式有问题
to this law firm not operating the way that it should
而我对此已经有点厌倦了
and me getting a little tired of it.
这才是原因
Now, that's all.
萨曼莎  你今晚看上去真美
Ah, Samantha. You look nice this evening.
别给我来这套  告诉我
Oh, don't give me that shit. You want to tell me
你为什么对一个才刚到我手里三小时的案子
why you set a motion to dismiss on a case for tomorrow
提出了明天就要陈述的不予受理申请
that I just got three hours ago?
我只是想帮你一把
I was just doing you a favor.
但如果你想取消掉  那随你便
But if you want to cancel it, you go right ahead.
-反正是你的案子  -什么叫帮我
- It's your case. - What do you mean a favor?
意思是我们有两周的时间来申请不予受理
I mean, we have two weeks to get this suit thrown out
但我们越早提出
but the faster we file it,
他们就越能感受到我们是认真的
the more serious they know we are.
然后就像你说的  如果我延期了
And of course now that you've said it, if I delay it,
-就会显得我没准备好  -你确实没有
- I look like I'm unprepared. - Which you are,
因为你不像我一样
because you haven't been their attorney
过去13年一直是他们的律师
for the last 13 years like I have.
我明白了
I get it.
如果我把这事告诉了罗伯特
And if I tell Robert what you did,
又会显得我很弱
I look weak.
但如果你让我帮你  我俩就都会显得很强
But if you let me help you, we both look strong.
你为什么不直接来找我
Why didn't you just come to me,
然后和我直说
and ask me to be let in on this?
因为我俩都知道你不会同意的
Because we both know that you would have said no.
不得不说  要不是我很了解你
I have to admit, if I didn't know any better
我会觉得你是个狠角色
I'd say you're a real badass.
如果这就让你觉得狠了
Well, if you think I'm a badass now,
你该等着看我们明天在法官面前
you just wait until we get that lead plaintiff
把主要原告干掉的场景
in front of the judge tomorrow.
-嗨  -别"嗨"了
- Hey. - Don't "Hey" me.
你把他们签下来了吗
Did you sign them?
当然  但你猜怎么着
Sure did, but get this.
这些人可不是什么
These guys aren't exactly
从大灰狼身边逃脱的小红帽
Little Red Riding Hood running away from the Big Bad Wolf.
-什么意思  -我们的第一项任务
- What are you talking about? - Our first assignment,
在我们把禁止令给帕克森送过去之后
after we send that cease and desist to Paxson
就是把他们的最佳员工骗入终身劳役的牢笼
is to trick their best employee into a lifetime of servitude.
别告诉我你在学迈克·罗斯
Don't tell me you're pulling a Mike Ross
-在我面前另有想法  -我只是想说
- and having second thoughts on me. - I'm just saying,
这件事情里可没什么好人
there aren't any saints in this situation.
但你猜怎么着  兄弟
But you know what, brother?
正因如此我们才能挣大钱
That's why we make the big bucks.
那就给我俩倒几杯酒
Well then, pour us a couple of drinks,
我现在就把禁止令传真过去
and I'll fax the cease and desist order right away.
你屁什么都不能传
You're not faxing shit.
你真以为
Do you really think that
你能和一个潜在客户见一次面
you can take a meeting with a prospective client,
然后试图整他们  而他们还一无所知吗
try to screw them over, and they wouldn't catch wind of it?
我不在乎他们知不知道
I don't care if they caught wind of it.
他们对此什么办法也没有
There's nothing that they can do about it.
放屁  他们能让所有的大金主知道
Bullshit, they can let every major player know
我们对我们的客户不诚信
that we don't deal with our clients in good faith.
但他们很体面地愿意给我们一次机会
But they have the decency to give us a chance
让我们在他们出手前拨乱反正
to make it right before they do,
你要抓住这次机会
and you're going to take it.
如果我没理解错你的意思...
If you're saying what I think you're saying--
我的意思是  放弃那家小公司
I'm saying drop the small potato,
按照你一开始说好的那样签下帕克森
and sign Paxson like you said you would in the first place.
你想扯不诚信这事吗  我们一过去
You want to talk bad faith? We went in there
他们就只想让我们犯罪
and they all but asked us to commit a crime.
那就别签他们  但你也不能
Then don't sign them. But what you don't do
利用从他们那里得来的消息
is go using the information that you got from them
去签下他们想要整的公司
to sign a guy that they were going after.
如果我没记错的话  我想签谁
And the last time I checked, I can sign
就能签谁
whoever the hell I want to sign.
哈维  房东那件事我可以放你一马
Harvey, I cut you some slack on that landlord thing.
但运营这家律所的是我  不是你
But I'm running this firm, not you.
我说什么你就得照办
You're going to do what I tell you to do.
你是不是连我穿什么样的西装也要管
You going to tell me what suit to wear, too?
听我说
Listen to me.
明早我来的时候  帕克森得是我们的客户了
Tomorrow morning, I come in, Paxson's our client.
这个话题到此为止
And I'm done discussing this topic.
哈维  也许这事不值得
Harvey, maybe it isn't worth it.
放松  一旦他意识到了那家小公司其实不小之后
Relax, he'll calm down once he realizes
他会冷静下来的
that small potato is not so small.
你疯了吗  这可是违抗命令
Are you crazy? This is about chain of command.
我们一开始之所以签下那些人
And the only reason we signed those guys
就是想给他留个好印象
in the first place was to impress him.
你之前不是还希望我
And you were the one who wanted me
有种和他对抗吗
to have the balls to stand up to him.
我不在乎什么违抗命令
Well, I don't give a shit what the chain of command is.
我现在是不可能让步的
There's no way I'm backing down now.
哈维  我告诉过你了
Harvey, I told you,
这些人可不是什么好人
it's not like these guys are saints.
他们让我对那个人做的事...
What they're having me do to this guy--
亚历克斯  够了
Alex, that's enough.
我对你的事后诸葛不感兴趣
I'm not interested in you second guessing me,
对你是因为赞恩才这么做
and I'm sure as shit not interested
就更不感兴趣了
in you doing it on Zane's behalf.
所以你到底想不想喝一杯
So you want to have a drink
庆祝签下了一个新客户
and celebrate signing a new client or not?
罗伯特  你怎么在这里
Robert, what are you doing here?
我来这里是因为现在已经是"明早"了
I'm here because it's tomorrow morning,
但你还没有签下帕克森
and you didn't sign Paxson yet.
听着  罗伯特
Look, Robert,
在我看来  这是你和哈维之间的事
as far as I'm concerned, this is between you and Harvey.
现在我就让这事变成你和我之间的事
Well, I'm making it between you and me.
什么意思
What are you saying?
意思是你是个聪明人
I'm saying you're a smart guy,
我俩都清楚你最后在这家律所会达到什么高度
and we both know what your endgame is at this firm.
如果你希望梦想成真
If you want that game to be a reality,
你就得照我说的做
you do what I need you to do.
你是在拿我的工作威胁我吗
Are you threatening my job?
我是在告诉你现实是怎样的
I'm telling you how it is.
你欺骗了那个客户
You dealt with that client in bad faith,
但我却对你以德报怨
and I'm doing you a courtesy by dealing with you in good faith.
给我的感觉可不是这样的
It sure doesn't feel like it.
我不是让你随便玩
I didn't say I was giving you kid gloves,
我是在光明正大地竞争
I said I was playing you straight.
说实话  我一向欣赏你
The truth is I like you, always have.
但是如果你在这件事上做不对的话
But if you don't get yourself on the right of this thing,
你不会比你现在的位置走得更远了
you're never going to go further than you are right now.
-罗伯特  -放弃他们
- Robert-- - Drop them.
我不想再听你辩解了
I don't want to hear another goddamn thing about it.
我们的计划是什么
Okay, what's our plan?
听好了  他们还不知道
Okay, listen up. They don't know it,
但我们要提交变更审判地点的申请
but we're going to file for a change of venue
加上撤案动议
in addition to our motion to dismiss.
我不明白
I don't understand.
变更审判地点到奥马哈并不能帮助我们
Changing the venue to Omaha doesn't help us.
那里的法律更严
The laws are harsher there.
没关系  因为陪审团不会
Doesn't matter, because the jury won't be.
什么意思
What do you mean?
这起官司并不是由随便
This lawsuit wasn't just filed
一群不满的背包客发起的
by a random bunch of disgruntled backpackers.
-是策划好的  -是谁
- It was orchestrated. - By who?
我们最大的竞争对手
Our biggest competitor.
正巧奥马哈是他们以前的总部
And it just so happens Omaha used to be their headquarters.
现在是个废弃的城市  我们去奥马哈搞他们
Which is now a ghost town. We go after them in Omaha,
好好收拾他们一顿
they're going to get their asses kicked.
并且他们没有理由反对变更审判地点
And they'll have no grounds to fight the change of venue,
因为明面上看  这是不利于我们的
because on the face of it, it's against our interests.
-正是  -路易  这招太机智了
- Exactly. - Louis, this is genius.
我知道  如我所说
Yeah, I know. But like I said,
你现在觉得我机智  等着看吧
you think I'm a genius now, you just wait.
因为今天结束之前  他们会付给我们钱
Because by the end of today, they're going to be paying us.
全体起立
All rise.
不好  我最老的客户有件急事找我
Oh, shit, I have an emergency with my oldest client.
-你能搞定吗  -没问题
- You sure you got this? - Oh, I got this.
我替你感到遗憾
I just feel bad for you
因为你没法看到了
because you're not going to get to see it.
好的
All right.
我们有一项撤案动议
We're here for a motion to dismiss.
利特先生  你有文件吗
Mr. Litt, do you have your paperwork?
法官大人  抱歉
Your Honor, I'm sorry,
但是由于获知了最新消息
but due to recent information coming to light,
-我们需要更改动议为变更审判地点  -什么
- we need to alter our motion to change of venue. - What?
他们没有理由这么做
They have--they have no basis for that.
我们有  法官大人
We believe we do, Your Honor.
所以我们想传唤首席原告
Which is why we'd like to call their lead plaintiff to the stand.
-介意我插个队吗  -视情况而定  很急吗
- Mind if I cut in? - That depends, is it urgent?
实话说是的
To tell you the truth, it is.
赞恩已经认为我越界了
Zane already thinks I overstep my bounds.
此时我最不想让他觉得
The last thing I need is for him to think
我连自己的作业都没法按时交
that I can't hand in my homework on time, too.
如果他这么看你
Well, if that's what he thinks about you,
你可以先用复印机
you can have the copier,
去他妈的罗伯特·赞恩
and Robert Zane can go ---- himself.
你还好吗
Hey. Everything okay?
-从没这么好过  -亚历克斯
- Never been better. - Alex.
我现在没心情  唐娜
I'm really not in the mood, Donna.
我知道  我不管
Yeah, I can see that, and I don't care.
-发生了什么事  -好吧  你知道吗
- What's going on? - All right, you want to know?
今早一来赞恩告诉我
First thing this morning, Zane tells me
除非我签了帕克森  我的名字永远挂不到墙上
unless I sign Paxson, my name's never going up on that wall.
什么  你告诉哈维了吗
What? Have you told Harvey about this?
告诉他有什么用
What good would it do?
就是哈维把我置于此地的
Harvey's the one who put me in this goddamn situation.
等等  我以为你同意签下
Wait, hang on a second, I thought you were on board
克莱托公司
with going after CrytoGen.
我不在乎我同意签谁
I don't give a shit what I was on board with.
当赞恩不想做的时候  我已经准备好退出
When Zane didn't want to do it, I was ready to back off.
-那就退出  -如果我这样做
- Then back off. - And I do that,
等于说我的名字永远也挂不到墙上了
I might as well kiss my chances at Name Partner good-bye,
亚历克斯  我觉得你没有给哈维足够的信任
Alex, I don't think you're giving Harvey enough credit.
这是他说的原话
He said, and I quote:
"我很确信  我对你代表罗伯特·赞恩质疑我
"I'm sure as shit not interested in you second guessing me
丝毫不感兴趣"
on Robert Zane's behalf."
-很好  -为什么很好
- Good. - What do you mean, good?
你在做"小林丸号"
《星舰迷航》故事中一个星舰学院的最终考试题目
I mean you're in a Kobayashi Maru.
这和寿司有什么关系
What the hell does sushi have to do with this?
不是寿司  来自于《星际迷航》
It's not sushi, it's from "Star Trek",
哈维总是提到它
and Harvey's been talking about it for a hundred years.
我一直以为是胡说八道  也许不是
I always thought it was bullshit, but maybe it's not.
-什么意思  -迟早
- What do you mean? - I mean, sooner or later,
所有人都会发现自己困在一个必输的处境
everyone finds themselves walled into a no-win situation.
这是你的难题  也是找到一条出路
This one's yours, and the way to prove yourself
向哈维和赞恩证明你自己的办法
to both Harvey and Zane is to find a way out anyway.
谢了  唐娜
Well, thanks, Donna.
我以为去哈佛上学才是领先的办法
And here I thought going to Harvard was the way to get ahead,
事实上  我应该看《星际迷航》系列的
when really, i should have just been watching old "Star Trek"S.
我没看
Well, I didn't,
除非答案在《美国警花》的剧集里...
so unless the answer is in an episode of "Cagney and Lacey"--
你知道吗  亚历克斯  我是想帮你
You know what, Alex? I'm trying to help you.
我告诉过你  我没心情
And I told you, I'm not in the goddamn mood.
好吧  我换一种方式给你说
Okay, then let me put it another way.
除非你想把名字挂到别处的墙上
Unless you think you can get your name on the wall someplace else,
我建议你不要担忧问题本身
I suggest you stop worrying about the problem,
开始思考解决的办法
and start worrying about the solution.
因为如果你找不到办法
Because if you can't find a way
脱离困境
to get yourself out of this situation,
也许你配不上冠名合伙人
maybe you don't deserve to be Name Partner after all.
拉森先生  你什么时候决定上诉的
So, Mr. Larson, when did you decide to file this lawsuit?
大概在我发现黑客盗取
About a week after I found out
我的个人信息一周后
hackers stole my information.
所以你很不安  之后联系了律师
So you were upset, and then, you contacted a lawyer.
事实上  我的律师联系了我
Actually, my attorney reached out to me.
这岂不是很方便
Oh, wasn't that convenient?
法官大人  游说客户可是犯罪
Your Honor, soliciting clients isn't a crime,
但和变更审判地点没有关系
and it's not relevant to change of venue.
不是吗  拉森先生  律师找到你的时候
But isn't it? Mr. Larson, when your lawyer approached you,
你要付多少律师费
what was the fee that you were quoted?
百分之十  如果官司打赢的话
Ten percent, contingent on winning.
你知道这类案子的正常收费
And are you aware that the normal fee
是你支付的三倍以上吗
for this type of case is three times that?
我并没有说不能还价
I'm not one to say no to a bargain.
你说的是我客户最大的对手
You mean the bargain where my client's biggest competitor
顺便付了你的律师费吗
was paying your lawyers on the side?
-什么  -反对  引导证人推测
- What? - Objection, speculative.
他回答了问题就不是推测了
It won't be when he answers the question.
法官大人  这是要干什么
Your Honor, where is this going?
我告诉你这是要干什么  法官大人
I'll tell you where it's going, Your Honor.
这是共谋
It's going to conspiracy charges
因为他接近他
because he approached him
来把我客户搞破产
to put my client out of business.
我没有...
I didn't--
-我没...  -回答问题
- I don't-- - Answer the question.
我没有问我的律师是怎么做到收支平衡的
I didn't ask how my lawyer makes his ends meet,
-因为我关注的是我的  -那来看看你的
- because I'm focused on mine. - Let's focus on yours.
因为如果我发现你知道他们在
Because if I find out that you knew they were driving
操控这场官司  而你撒了谎
this lawsuit, and you lied about it,
我会找你房子的麻烦
oh, I'm going to come for your house.
然后是养老金
And then, I'm going to come for your pension--
-反对  -还有你女儿的小猪存钱罐
- Objection. - And your daughter's piggy bank.
骚扰证人
Badgering.
我做的都是如果他没有说实话的情况下
I'm not doing anything a federal prosecutor won't do
-联邦检察官会做的事  -并不是
- if he doesn't tell the truth. - Yes, you are.
你拿枪指着我客户的头
You are pointing a gun at my client's head,
我很确定如果我拿枪指着你的头
and I'm pretty damn sure you wouldn't like it
你是不会喜欢的
if I pointed a gun at yours.
利特先生
Mr. Litt?
蹲下  把嘴闭上
Lay down and shut up.
这次你不把钱包
And this time, you don't give me your wallet
还有手机给我  闭上嘴的话
and give me your phone, and keep your mouth shut,
我就不仅仅是揍你了
I won't just kick you.
我会按下扳机
I'll pull this trigger,
你就再也见不到你在意的人了
and you'll never see anyone you care about ever again.
利特先生  最后问一次  你还有要说的吗
Mr. Litt, for the last time, do you have anything further?
驳回撤销指控和变更审判地点的动议
Motions to dismiss and change of venue are denied.
咱俩得谈谈  现在就得谈
You and I need to talk, and we need to talk right now.
不  不用
No, we don't.
如果你识趣的话  你就会出去
And if you know what's good for you, you'll get out.
在你向我解释清楚
I'm not going anywhere until you explain to me
前一分钟你还在订去奥马哈的单程票
how one minute, you're ready to book one-way tickets to Omaha,
后一分钟  我发现什么都没了是怎么回事前
and the next minute,
我是哪也不会去的
I find out we've all but lost.
你不在场  你不知道发生了什么
You weren't there. You don't know what happened.
我知道  所以我才来问
I know that. That's what I'm doing here.
-我说了  出去  -我说了
- And I told you to get out. - And I told you
在你告诉我发生了什么之前  我哪也不会去的
I'm not going anywhere until you tell me what happened.
听我说  我尽力了
Listen to me. I did the best I could,
我不想再谈这件事了
and I do not want to talk about this anymore.
你尽力了
The best you could?
你不是什么刚入行一年的律师
You're not some first-year associate.
你他妈是冠名合伙人
You're a goddamn Name Partner
一个在我的案子上仗势欺人的人
who bullied his way on to my case.
之后我知道的是  你就像条狗一样躺着
And the next thing I know, you've laid down like a dog,
-让别人欺辱你  -你不在场
- let yourself get kicked-- - You weren't there!
你不在
You weren't there.
你不知道我经历了什么
You don't know the shit I went through.
你永远都不会知道
You never will.
现在走开
Now back the hell off,
滚出我的办公室
and get the hell out of my office.
路易  放松  我只是想...
Louis, relax. I was just trying to--
滚出去
Get the hell out!
哈维  我能和你聊聊吗
Harvey, can I talk to you for a second?
当然可以  怎么了
Sure, what' s on your mind?
我刚刚接到了霍莉·科伦维尔的电话
I just got a call from Holly Cromwell.
别告诉我  有另一家公司
Don't tell me, she's got another firm
想要聘用你  你想拿这个当筹码
wanting to recruit you, and you're looking to leverage us.
-哈维  严肃点  -怎么了
- Harvey, this is serious. - What is it?
她告诉我亚历克斯·威廉姆斯给她打电话
She told me that Alex Williams called her up,
想看看他在市场上能得到什么
looking to see what he could get in the marketplace.
-胡扯  -不是胡扯
- Bullshit. - It's not bullshit.
他想知道他在别的地方
He wants to know what the odds are
当冠名合伙人的几率有多大
of him getting his name on the wall somewhere else.
我不相信  他怎么会这么对我
I don't believe it. How could he do this to me?
与其想他怎么能这么做
Maybe instead of thinking about how he could do this,
你不如想想为什么
you might want to think about why.
-我不在乎原因  -你应该在乎
- I don't care why. - Well, you should.
因为你把你和赞恩之间的事变成私人恩怨
Because you made it personal between you and Zane,
亚历克斯就成了个牺牲品
and Alex became nothing but an afterthought.
你是怎么知道这些事的
How do you even know about any of this?
因为在他和霍莉谈之前  他和我谈过
Because before he talked to Holly, he talked to me.
所以我知道赞恩今早去找亚历克斯
Which is why I know that Zane went to Alex
告诉他如果他不签帕克森
this morning and told him if he didn't sign Paxson,
他就永远都成不了冠名合伙人
he'd never make Name Partner here at all.
他在哪
Where is he?
哈维  如果你和赞恩对抗
Harvey, if you confront Zane,
情况只会更糟糕
it's just going to make things worse.
我不在乎  我不能让他
I don't care. I am not going to let him
这么欺负我的人
bully my guy into submission.
现在就把电话挂了
Hang up the phone right the hell now.
不要走进我的办公室这么和我说话
Don't walk into my office and tell me that.
所以我不能这样  但你就能这样
So I can't walk in but you can walk into
进入我的人的办公室  威胁他的职业生涯
my guy's office and threaten his career?
我没有威胁他的职业生涯  我只是实话实说
I didn't threaten his career. I just told him like it was.
-那不是你能决定的  -扯淡不是
- That's not your call. - Bullshit, it's not.
我给你下了命令  如果你不听
I gave you an order, and if you're not going to follow it,
我就去找下一个人
I'm going to the next man down.
如果他不听  他就拿不到我的票
And if he doesn't listen to me, he's never getting my vote.
所以他就得听你的
So he's got to listen to you,
但他不用听我的
but he doesn't have to listen to me?
你觉得经营合伙人是什么意思
What the hell do you think Managing Partner means?
如果这是它的含义的话
Well, if this is what it means,
那或许是我错了
then maybe I made a bad call
我不该高尚到拱手相让
in being gracious and letting you have it.
你并不高尚  你只是认清了现实
You weren't being gracious. You were recognizing reality.
你知道我在这方面做得比你好
Which is that I'm better at this than you.
至于你擅长的
And what you're better at
就是随时随地做任何你想做的事
is doing whatever you feel like doing at any goddamn minute.
我现在最想说的是
Well, what I feel like saying right now is,
亚历克斯是我的人
Alex is my guy.
他听我的  就这样
He does what I say, and that's final.
那很不巧
Well, that's too bad, because I didn't do
不管你们俩怎么说
what either one of you said,
现在木已成舟了
and it's too late to take it back.
我不相信
I don't believe this.
你是说你换工作了
Are you saying you took another job?
不  是我让某个人换了份工作
No, I'm saying I got someone else to take another job.
你到底在说些什么
What the hell are you talking about?
克莱托公司想让我骗他们最能干的员工
CrytoGen wanted me to trick their biggest asset
让他为他们工作一辈子
into a lifetime of servitude.
但我跟他说  他有出来单干的权利
Instead, I informed him of his right to go out on his own
他现在是我们最新签约的委托人
and signed him as our newest client.
你疯了吗  我让你签的是帕克森
Are you out of your mind? I told you to sign Paxson.
你给我们的理由是
And the reason you gave both of us
你不希望我们对他们居心叵测
was that you didn't want us dealing with them in bad faith.
所以我们没有
Well, now we didn't.
我们只是开了个会  选择不与他们签约
All we did was take a meeting and not sign them.
但你还是没做我吩咐的事情
And you still didn't do what I asked.
我要求的你也没做
And you didn't do what I asked, either.
我确实没有  如果你们想要的是个
You're right, I didn't. Because if all you want
只会点头哈腰的人   那要我干什么
is a yes man, then what the hell am I doing here?
-你听着  -不  你听着
- You listen to me. - No, you listen to me.
我签了一个将来会对公司
I signed a client that's going to be worth
有巨大价值的客户
a huge amount to this firm.
我是个出色的律师
I'm a hell of a goddamn lawyer,
如果你们连这点都意识不到
and if you can't see that,
那我的名字就不必跟二位的一起出现了
then I don't want to have my name next to yours.
-亚历克斯  -不  这些话必须说
- Alex-- - No, I said what I had to say.
我觉得  你们俩是时候认真工作了
As far as I'm concerned, you two need to work your shit out.
我不知道你的想法
I don't know about you,
但我还挺喜欢他生气的样子的
but I kind of like the guy when he's angry.
你当然会了
Yeah, you would,
这跟你对杰西卡的态度
because that's the same flavor of bullshit
如出一辙
that you served Jessica.
又怎么了
What now?
我得跟你谈谈你搭档的问题
I need to talk to you about your partner.
-你说罗伯特  -是路易·利特
- You mean Robert? - I mean Louis Litt.
-他怎么了  -他有点不对劲
- What about him? - Something's wrong with him.
在你说我不了解他之前
And before you tell me I don't know him,
我告诉你  这件事真的不寻常
I'm telling you, this isn't normal behavior.
就算是对他那样的男人来说
Even for a man with his reputation.
-你怎么知道  -不如我先说
- How can you know that? - How about I start by saying
他在和罗伯特·赞恩的会议上
he stood up his own clients
为自己的委托人辩护
at a meeting with Robert Zane?
后来不知道为什么  银行那个案子
And then somehow shit the bed in court
他在法庭上吓傻了
on a case he had in the bank.
我都不想提
And I'm not even going to get into
我问他这些的时候他是什么态度
how he treated me when I tried to ask him about it.
还有其他人知道这些事吗
Does anyone else know about any of this?
从他秘书的表情看
Judging by the look I saw on his secretary's face,
她应该也知道
I'd say she does.
但她一个字都不会跟我说的
I'd also say she's not going to tell me a thing.
为什么你来告诉我  而不是罗伯特
Why are you telling me about this, and not Robert?
因为就算我是新来的
Because I may be new here,
我也看得出谁和谁是朋友
but I know what friendship looks like.
现在我告诉你  路易·利特需要朋友
And right now, I'm telling you. Louis Litt needs a friend.
-哈维  -路易
- Harvey. - Louis.
晚上有安排吗
You got any plans tonight?
不如一起出去吃个饭
I was thinking we could go out for dinner.
我今天没空
Oh, that's not going to work for me.
-我要回家陪希拉  -拜托
- I have to get home to Sheila. - Oh, come on.
我们有点事要谈谈
We've got some stuff to catch up on.
-什么事  -据我所知
- What stuff? - From what I hear,
你最近几天有点不顺
you've had a rough couple days.
没事  哈维  没什么好担心的
It's all good, Harvey. Nothing to worry about.
没事  你骗谁
All good? Come on.
我可不经常请你吃饭
I ask you to dinner once in a blue moon,
一般只要我开口  你从来不拒绝
and whenever I do, you drop everything.
过去是这样  但我现在有希拉了
I used to, but I have Sheila now,
没事我就先告辞了
so if you'll excuse me.
不说实话不许走
You're not leaving until I get an answer.
别拿希拉做挡箭牌
Don't hide behind Sheila.
-放开我  -怎么了  路易
- Get the hell off me! - What's going on, Louis?
-没什么  -有事你可以跟我说
- Nothing. - You can talk to me.
你想让我说什么
About what,
-根本没事  -为什么在法庭上会那样
- there's nothing-- - Why'd you roll over in court?
-为什么你不来吃晚餐  -别说了
- Why'd you no-show at dinner? - Please stop.
为什么你要让我停下  路易
Why do you need me to stop, Louis?
-你在害怕什么  -我被抢劫了
- What are you so scared of? - God damn it, I was mugged.
我被抢劫了  我以为我会死  行了吗
I was mugged, and I thought I was going to die, okay?
那个人用枪
He had a gun...
顶着我的后脑勺
that he had pressed to the back of my head.
我到现在还能感觉到
I can still feel it.
你就想听这个吗  那这就是事情经过
Is that what you want to hear? Because that's what's going on.
没事了  伙计  你没事了
It's okay, buddy. You're okay.
但我有事  哈维  我已经一团糟了
But it's not okay, Harvey. It's not, I'm a mess.
换我也会这样  每个人都会
I'd be a mess, too. Anyone would.
如果我没办法摆脱这种感觉怎么办
What if it doesn't go away?
会好的
It will.
我不知道这要花多久
I don't know how long it will take,
我也不知道你什么时候才能走出来
or when it'll happen,
但我确定的是
but I know one thing.
如果你不说出来  它就永远不会过去
It won't go away if you don't talk about it,
-你需要的不只是治疗  -哈维
- and I don't just mean therapy. - Harvey--
你身边有人在关心你
Look, you have people here who care about you.
出了事不要瞒着他们
Don't hide it from them.
但这件事我不会告诉罗伯特
I'm not telling Robert.
-为什么不  -因为你是我的朋友
- Why not? - Because you're my friend,
而他是我的老板  初来乍到
and he's my boss, and he just got here,
我不想让他认为我很软弱
and I cannot have him see me as weak.
他不会认为这是软弱
He won't think you're weak.
他会觉得能说出口就是一种坚强
He'll think you're strong for telling him.
但我没办法坚强  我会一副软弱相
But I won't be strong. I'm going to turn into this.
看看我  哈维  看看我
Look at me, Harvey. Look at me.
我不能让他看到我这幅样子
I can't have him see me like this.
不如我替你告诉他
Why don't I tell him for you?
我本身也要找他
We've got some things to work out between us anyway.
谢谢你哈维  那就太好了
Thank you, Harvey. That would be nice.
罗伯特·赞恩
-怎么了  唐娜  -罗伯特  你要的汇报
- What is it, Donna? - Robert, I have your report.
但你看之前  我得再跟你重复
But before you read it, I need to tell you
我告诉过你的一件事
what I told you before.
这不是我的专长
This isn't really what I do.
-那为什么给我  -因为你要了
- Why bring it to me at all? - Because you asked for it.
更重要的是  我做的是你需要的
And more importantly, what I do is what you need right now.
我理一下
So let me get this straight.
你带着一个站不住脚的借口进来
You're going to come in here with a half-assed
给我交报告  还要指教我需要什么
excuse for a report, and then tell me what I need?
是的  因为在你要求我
Yeah, I am, because while you wanted me
做你本可以找会计事务所
to be spending my time on something you could have hired
完成的工作时  我正忙着
an accounting firm for, I was busy working my ass off
用老办法最大化每平方英尺收益
maximizing revenue per square foot the old fashioned way.
-也就是避免这里崩溃  -你在说什么
- By keeping this place together. - What are you talking about?
我在说在你忙着跟哈维挑起战争
I'm just saying that between picking a fight with Harvey,
从路易那里抢客户
taking a client away from Louis,
或者其他什么事时
and whatever else you've been up to,
你都没发现你的重要律师
you didn't notice that one of your star attorneys
都在考虑辞职了
was thinking about leaving.
多亏了我  他才考虑留下
And now, thanks to me, he's going to stay.
你在说亚历克斯吗
You're talking about Alex?
是的  当然是他
Yes, of course I'm talking about Alex.
那么唐娜  我感激你做的事
Then Donna, I appreciate what you did.
但他要是走了也就走了
But if he left, he left. So be it.
因为要我领导这个公司
Because if I'm going to lead this firm,
这里的人就得听我的话
people need to follow my orders.
也许问题不在命令  罗伯特
Maybe the problem isn't with the orders, Robert,
也许是在下命令的人
Maybe it's with the man who's giving them.
你可能不爱听  但我还是得说
You may not want to hear this, but I'm going to say it anyway.
你认为兰德和考德背叛你
You think that the reason Rand and Kaldor turned on you
是因为你对我们心软了
is because you had a soft spot for us.
我认为其实是因为你对他们没有
I think it's because you didn't have a soft spot for them.
如果你像对待他们那样对待我们
And if you treat us the way you treated them,
历史将会重演
the same thing's going to happen here.
我不能让每个人都随心所欲
I can't just let everyone do what they want.
那不是我
It's not in me.
我只是说  有时候我们需要管理
I'm just saying, sometimes we need to be smacked in line,
而有时候  你需要让我们
and sometimes, you need to let us do
按我们的方式来办事
what we do the way we do it.
每平方英尺收益的事我会交给
I'm going to farm out this revenue per square foot
会计事务所
to an accounting firm.
谢谢  罗伯特
Thanks, Robert.
怎么
What?
我一直知道你对哈维会来这招
I knew you did this whisperer shit with Harvey,
但我没想到你也会对我用
but I didn't think you'd ever do it to me.
告诉你个小秘密  赞恩
I'm going to let you in on a little secret, Zane.
我对谁都用
I do it to everybody.
亚历克斯  有时间吗
Alex, you got a second?
看你来找我干什么了
That depends on what you're here to say.
我来道歉
I'm here to say I'm sorry.
我让你陷入了一个不该你陷入的不利境地
I put you in a position that I shouldn't have,
但我也想说哦
but I also want to say
你没必要去找猎头
you didn't have to talk to that headhunter.
-是的  哈维  我有  -为什么
- Yeah, Harvey, I did. - Why?
你真想知道
You want to know the truth?
我想知道我有什么筹码
I had to know what kind of leverage I had.
结果是  没人愿意比你更快地
And it turns out, there wasn't anybody willing
把我的名字放墙上
to put my name on the wall any faster than you.
所以我只能接受唐娜的胡扯
Which is what left me open to hear Donna's bullshit.
什么叫唐娜的胡扯
What do you mean Donna's bullshit?
其实是你的胡扯
It's really your bullshit.
她说我在一个两败俱伤的境地
She said I was in a no-win situation,
我或者可以抱怨
and I could bitch and moan about it,
或者想办法解决
or I could get out of it myself.
-小林丸  -是的
- Kobayashi Maru. - Yeah.
你的解决办法很高明
Yeah, well, you got yourself out pretty damn well,
而且也不是只有我这么想
and I'm not the only one who thinks so.
赞恩也很欣赏
Zane was pretty impressed, too.
看来任务我算是完成了
Then I guess I got the job done.
看来也许我是该看看
And maybe I should have watched a little "Star Trek"
-《星际迷航》  -什么
- growing up after all. - What?
你居然没看过《星际迷航》
How could you never watch "Star Trek?"
这部剧剧情傻演员丑
Because it's a stupid show with shitty effects.
你知道我喜欢它对吗
You realize I love that show, right?
我才不管你怎么想
I don't care how you feel about it.
这部剧剧情傻演员丑
It's a stupid show with shitty effects.
告诉你  亚历克斯  也许你是个好律师
You know what, Alex? You may be a hell of a lawyer,
但如果你无法欣赏《星际迷航》
but if you can't appreciate the original "Star Trek,"
那你什么也不是  因为柯克船长
you're nothing, because Captain Kirk
是电视荧幕上最成功的角色没有之一
is the best television character ever created.
我就两个字给你  混蛋
I've got two words for you, mother----er.
夏威夷神探
Magnum, P.I.
那些都是战斗宣言  你知道的对吧
Those are fighting words. You know that, right?
不是战斗宣言  是对酒宣言  哈维
They're not fighting words, Harvey, they're drinking words.
所以坐下  我们想象
So sit on down, and let's hash this out
两个人怎么一起
like two people who can both appreciate "M-A-S-H."
听起来不错
Sounds good to me.
-罗伯特  -在你说话之前
- Robert. - Before you say anything,
让我先为我的做法道歉
let me just say that I'm sorry for what happened,
很抱歉我对待你的态度
and I'm more sorry for how I treated you.
谢谢  罗伯特
I appreciate that, Robert.
但这是我的错误  不是你的
But this was my fault, not yours.
路易  这不是你的错
Louis, this is not your fault.
我想让你知道你可以来找我的
And I want you to know you could have come to me.
我觉得很无力
I just felt so powerless.
当然了  你是受害人
Of course you did. You were a victim.
但那并不代表你需要觉得自己是
But that doesn't mean you have to feel like one.
那怎么可能
How can I not feel like one?
路易  我跟你说一个谁都不知道的秘密
Louis, I'm going to tell you something nobody knows.
我长大的街区很乱
I grew up in a rough place with rough people.
别告诉我你理解被打劫是什么感受
Don't tell me that you know what it's like to get mugged?
不  我想告诉你的是
No, what I'm trying to tell you is
-我理解另一边的感受  -什么
- I know what it's like to be on the other end of it. - What?
当时我14岁
I was 14 years old.
当时的我只有朋友  我很爱他们
My friends were all I knew, and I loved them.
但他们当时状态也很不好
But they were messed up.
有天晚上  他们就有了
And one night, they get it in their heads
打劫的想法
that they're going to roll somebody,
我也参与了
and I got caught up in it.
那个人反抗了  我们没有选择
The guy fought back. We had no choice.
我们狠揍了他一顿  他进了医院
We beat him good, put him in the hospital.
-天哪  -是的
- Jesus. - I know.
我只干过一次
And I only did it once,
而我后悔了一辈子
and it's haunted me my whole life.
现在也是
It still does.
你是说我应该为打劫我的人
Are you saying that I should feel sorry
感到遗憾吗
for the man who mugged me?
不不不  我不是这个意思  路易
No, no, no, I'm not saying that, Louis.
我只是说有一天
I'm saying that someday,
他也必须面对自己的良心债
he's going to have to face up to who he is,
而他也要一辈子背负愧疚
and he'll carry that shame for a lifetime.
但你不用
But you don't have to,
因为这件事和你是什么样的人
because this doesn't have a single thing
一点关系都没有
to do with who you are.
-听到了吗  -听到了吗
- You hearing me? - I'm hearing you.
好的  还有路易  我们是一家人
Good, and Louis, we are a family here.
所以从现在起  我希望你记住
So from now on, I want you to remember
什么事你都可以跟家人说
you can share things with your family.
-好的  -看在上帝份上
- Okay. - I mean, for God's sake.
你都没有犹豫  就告诉了我
You didn't think twice about telling me
-你窃听你喜欢的人的事  -有道理
- you were tapping your woman. - That's a fair point.
好伙计
Uh, okay. Good man.
你今晚回家吗
You heading home for the night?
-回  怎么了  -我想跟你说
- I was, why? - I just wanted to let you know
我跟亚历克斯谈了  一切都好
I talked to Alex, and that it's all good.
-很好  哈维  -还有一件事
- That's great, Harvey. - There's just one thing.
其实不是他联系了霍莉·科伦维尔
It turns out that he didn't call Holly Cromwell.
-是她联系的他  -所以呢
- She called him. - So?
所以如果如此  她为什么又联系你
So, if she called him, why would she then call you
-说是他联系她的  -有道理
- and say he called her? - I guess she wouldn't.
可能是我打给她  让她联系他的
I guess I must have called her, and told her to call him.
-能问问为什么吗  -因为  哈维
- Mind if I ask why? - Because, Harvey.
有时候人们需要清楚自己的立场
Sometimes people just need to know where they stand.
要是他有能力在别的公司
And what if he'd been able to leverage himself
当上冠名合伙人呢
into Name Partner somewhere else?
那你和罗伯特·赞恩就会知道
Then you and Robert Zane would learn
如果你们处理不好自己的事
that if you can't figure your shit out,
受伤的只会有你们自己
the only people who are going to get hurt are you.
萨曼莎  你在这里做什么
Samantha, what are you doing here?
我想跟你谈谈
I want to talk to you.
如果是因为之前
Look, if this is about earlier--
是因为之前的事  但不是你想的那样
It is about earlier, but not how you think.
我来告诉你发生在你身上的事
I came here to tell you that the same thing
也曾发生在我身上
that happened to you happened to me.
-罗伯特告诉你的是吗  -是的
- Robert told you, didn't he? - He did.
当时  是他帮了我
And when it happened, he was there for me.
所以现在我来帮你
So now, I'm going to be there for you.
抱歉  他怎么帮你的
I'm sorry, what do you mean he was there for you?
不重要  重要的是
That's not important. What is important
你要开始学自卫术
is you're going to start learning self-defense.
就从现在开始
And you're going to start right now.
我很感激你来一趟  好吗
I really appreciate you coming by, okay?
但我要进去了
But I'm going to go inside.
跟我说实话
Tell me the truth.
看到我站在这里  而你还没看出
When you saw me standing there, and you couldn't make out
是不是我的时候  你怕了  对吗
whether it was me or not, you were scared, right?
我不想学自卫术
I don't want to learn self-defense.
帮帮忙  试着打我
Do me a favor. Try to hit me.
-我不想打你  -你打一下试试
- I'm not going to hit you. - Try to hit me.
好的
Okay.
准备好了吗  砰
Ready? Boop.
-太疯狂了  简直  -你能不能
- That's pretty crazy, right-- - Would you just
-好好打  -好吧好吧
- try to hit me? - All right, fine.
好了  妈妈
All right, mother--
天哪
Oh, my God.
你能杀人的吧
You could kill someone, couldn't you?
有可能  重要的是  他们杀不了我
Probably, but the point is, they couldn't kill me.
起来  你该上第一课了
Now, get up, it's time for your first lesson.
首先  要清楚周围的环境
First things first, you got to be aware of your surroundings,
你要知道怎么站稳
and you got to learn how to stand.
好的
Okay.
-教教我  -好
- Show me. - Okay.
要把重心放稳
You want to stabilize your core,
一只脚在另一只前面一点点
so one foot slightly behind the other,
与胯部同宽
about hip-width apart.
-知道为什么稳了吗  -重心
- See how it stabilizes? - The core.
-是的  -好的  我这个动作
- Yeah. - Okay, so how many calories
消耗了多少大卡
have I burned just now?
三卡
Three.
因为你话太多
Just because you're talking so much.
-好的好的  -好
- Right, okay. - Yeah.
好的
All right.
打我
Now smack me.